Dimitri Nakos

2340 Greenland Ave. Charlotte, NC 28208 Portfolio

704-904-9661 <u>dimi1nakos@gmail.com</u>

Summary

Currently enrolled in the UNC at Charlotte Full-Stack web development boot camp with a focus on JavaScript and React. Coming from the automotive industry where I spent 8 years developing problem solving skills, time management, led teams, and have trained new hires. I look forward to transferring these skills to a new career in Web Development.

Projects

◆ Hiking Trail Locator Web App – github repo

An application that utilizes open source APIs to interact with each other in order create a user friendly experience.

◆ Retro Backlog – github repo

Full-Stack application working with JavaScript, node.js, heroku, and mysql.

♦ Weather Dashboard – github repo

A weather tracking web app that utilizes JavaScript to dynamically create HTML elements with corresponding data.

Education

◆ UNC at Charlotte Full-Stack Coding Boot camp

Currently enrolled

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, node, and React.

C.	ki	ш	
	ΚI	ш	•
\sim		ш	

Problem Solver Time Management Team Leader
Git / Git Bash Detail Oriented Studied UI/UX
JavaScript HTML/CSS Node

Work History

♦ Automotive Technician, Keffer Volkswagen

December 2017 – Present

Troubleshoot and problem solve issues with emerging automotive technologies.

Utilize web based training and information.

Coordinated group brainstorming for difficult diagnosis.

Trained new technicians starting out in the field.

Performed accurate and timely diagnosis and repairs.

♦ Automotive Technician, South Charlotte Hyundai

August 2016 – December 2017

Performed detail oriented inspections.

Inspected every brand new vehicle with emphasis on detail.

Mediated between the customers and service writers.

Supervised and assigned tasks to technicians.

♦ Automotive Technician, Carolina Volkswagen

January 2011 – August 2017

Started from no experience to become one of the top technicians in the service department within a year. Delegated tasks to technicians. Informed customers of services provided and necessary tasks required.

References

♦ Davis Sithideth

846-316-5554 NASCAR Web Development Team

♦ Brian Moyer

704-488-0915 Keffer Volkswagen, Service manager

♦ Ronnie Taylor

704-604-9446 Keffer Volkswagen, Master Technician